cracks4win.com 2019-09-28

# Privacy Policy | Cracks4Win

****

## _PRIVACY POLICY OF CRACKS4WIN_

Welcome to cracks4win (the “Site”).

We understand that privacy online is important to users of our Site, especially when conducting business. This statement governs our privacy policies with respect to those users of the Site (“Visitors”) who visit without transacting business and Visitors who register to transact business on the Site and make use of the various services offered by cracks4win (collectively, “Services”) (“Authorized Customers”).

At www.cracks4win.com we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use ‘cracks4win.com’ and how we safeguard your information.

Our website address is: https://www.cracks4win.com.

## What personal data we collect and why we collect it

When you interact with our Site, and/or Services, we collect Information that, alone or in combination with other data, could be used to identify you (“Personal Data”). Some of the Information we collect is stored in a manner that cannot be linked back to you (“Non-Personal Data”).

### Comments

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

### Media

If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.

### Contact forms

When a user submit a contact form by using cracks4win.com we collect Information including user name, email address, subject and message. This information’s is stored for few months. We never use this information’s in other purpose.

### Cookies

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

### Embedded content from other websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

## How long we retain your data

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

## What rights you have over your data

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

## Where we send your data

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.

### What third parties we receive data from

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. The ads may contain cookies which may be used by the advertising companies to better understand a visitor’s preferences and help them to display related ads. However, the cookies received with the advertisements are collected by the advertising company and we do not have access to that information.These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

 **Email Addresses – We never share your email addresses with anyone.**  
Cookies and Web Beacons – We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, or email address) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and would like to know your options in relation to·not having this information used by these companies.

### Does Cracks4Win sell or rent my Personal Data?

No, Cracks4win does not sell or rent your Personal Data At All.

 ****WARNING** By Using Our Products!!**

By using our products, if anything wrong happen to your computer or laptop, then **Cracks4Win admin** is not responsible for any kind of damage. Because it was your choices and your decision. You should check each and every section before using our products to know more such as- how to use and how to download etc.. **Before downloading any kind of product from cracks4win website please check our download section** – ‘[ **How To Download**](https://www.cracks4win.com/how-to-download-from-cracks4win-2/)‘.

© 2017-2019 **cracks4win** , All rights reserved.  
Unauthorized duplication or publication of any materials  
from this Site is expressly prohibited.
